<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="log.xsl"?>
<log>
	<post>
		<body>Hello world! <bold>bold</bold></body>
		<author>Mateus</author>
		<datetime>0</datetime>
		<categories>
			<tag>Test</tag>
		</categories>
	</post>
	
	<post>
		<body>
			To undo git add before a commit, run git reset file.c or git reset to unstage all changes.
			<citation>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-undo-a-git-add/</citation>
		</body>
		<author>Mateus</author>
		<datetime>2021/09/11 19:55:17</datetime>
		<categories>
			<tag>git</tag>
		</categories>
	</post>
	
	<post>
		<body>
			XML/XLST does not work on local machine due to CORS.<citation>https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/questions/1264318</citation>
		</body>
		<author>Mateus</author>
		<datetime>2021/09/11 20:06:07</datetime>
		<categories>
			<tag>Web development</tag>
		</categories>
	</post>
	
	<post>
		<body>
			In Rust, variables are not initialized by default, because there is no sensible default for every type.<citation>https://users.rust-lang.org/t/use-of-possibly-uninitialized-variable-on-an-initialized-variable/4799/2</citation>
			Rust is designed to be memory safe. It does not permit null pointers, dangling pointers, or data races.[52][53][54] Data values can be initialized only through a fixed set of forms, all of which require their inputs to be already initialized.[55] To replicate pointers being either valid or NULL, such as in linked list or binary tree data structures, the Rust core library provides an option type, which can be used to test whether a pointer has Some value or None.[53] Rust has added syntax to manage lifetimes, which are checked at compile time by the borrow checker. Unsafe code can subvert some of these restrictions using the unsafe keyword.[15]<citation>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rust_(programming_language)</citation>
			<hr/>
			Ada has null pointers, run-time accessibility checks (Rust does it on compile time), variable initialization to default values.
			<bold>A program written in Rust will probably crash less than a program written in Ada.</bold>
			Ada uses Unchecked_Deallocation; Rust does not require manual memmory management or a GC.
			Ada has integer ranges.
			<hr/>
			Tony Hoare apologized for inventing the null reference. He calls it the billion-dollar mistake.<citation>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tony_Hoare</citation>
		</body>
		<author>Mateus</author>
		<datetime>2021/09/12 16:51:27</datetime>
		<categories>
			<tag>Programming languages</tag>
			<tag>Security</tag>
		</categories>
	</post>
</log>
